tvfcu.com 2019-06-29

# FACTS

                                                                                                     Rev. 12/31/2018
                            WHAT DOES TENNESSEE VALLEY FEDERAL CREDIT UNION
FACTS                       DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?                        Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law
                            gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also
                            requires us to tell you how we collect, share and protect your personal information.
                            Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?                       The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or
                            service you have with us. This information can include:
                              Social Security number and income
                              Account balances and payment history
                              Credit history and overdraft history
                            When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as
                            described in this notice.
How?                        All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their
                            everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies
                            can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Tennessee Valley
                            Federal Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                                                              Can you limit this
      Reasons we can share your personal information                 Does TVFCU share?
                                                                                                   sharing?
For our everyday business purposes —                                        Yes                       No
such as to process your transactions, maintain your
account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations,
or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes —                                                Yes                       No
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial companies                          Yes                       Yes
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes —                            Yes                       Yes
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes —                            Yes                       Yes
information about your creditworthiness
For our affiliates to market to you                                         Yes                       Yes
For non-affiliates to market to you                                         Yes                       Yes
To limit                      Call (423) 634-3600 or toll free (800) 634-3600
                              Visit us online: www.tvfcu.com/u/optout
our sharing                 Please Note:
                            If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the
                            date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to
                            share your information as described in this notice. However, you can contact us at
                            any time to limit our sharing.
Questions?                  Call (423) 634-3600 or toll free (800) 634-3600.

                                                                                                 Rev. 12/31/2018
Page 2
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?      Tennessee Valley Federal Credit Union (TVFCU)
What we do
How does Tennessee Valley          To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use,
Federal Credit Union protect my    we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures
personal information?              include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
                                   We will partner only with those businesses that follow strict
                                   confidentiality requirements. You also have a responsibility to safeguard
                                   your financial information at all times.
How does Tennessee Valley          We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Federal Credit Union collect my      Open an account
personal information?                Apply for a loan
                                     Pay your bills
                                     Use your credit or debit card
                                     Make deposits or withdrawals from your account
                                   We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit
                                   bureaus, affiliates or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?     Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                     Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes — information
                                        about your creditworthiness
                                     Affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                     Sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
                                   State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                                   limit sharing.
What happens when I limit sharing Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
for an account I hold jointly with
someone else?
Definitions
Affiliates                         Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                   financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                   Our affiliates include financial companies, such as:
                                     Tennessee Valley Investment Advisors
Non-affiliates                     Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                   financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                   Non-affiliates we share with can include:
                                     Mortgage companies
                                     Insurance companies
                                     Direct marketing companies
                                     Nonprofit organizations
Joint marketing                    A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that
                                   together market financial products or services to you.
                                   Our joint marketing partners include:
                                     Credit card companies
                                     Insurance companies
